<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>./sk4d</title>
    <link>https://sk4d.tk/</link>
    <description>Recent content on ./sk4d</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 17:30:38 +0630</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sk4d.tk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>valentine Writeup [hxpCTF 23]</title>
      <link>https://sk4d.tk/posts/valentine-hxpctf2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 17:30:38 +0630</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sk4d.tk/posts/valentine-hxpctf2023/</guid>
      <description>tl;dr
SSTI in the valentine card bypass filter by setting ejs delimiter option RCE :yay: intro I played hxpCTF 2023 last weekend with my team bi0s. There a were a lot of awesome web challenges. I have worked on most of the web challenges and this is the write-up for the challenge valentine
Initial analysis The application lets us to create a fully customisable valentines card. The application asks us to personalize our card using the &amp;lt;%= name %&amp;gt; tags and it gets replaced with the value in the name parameter we send to the template, this can be seen in the source</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>scorescope Writeup [DiceCTF 23]</title>
      <link>https://sk4d.tk/posts/scorescope-dicectf-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 14:41:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sk4d.tk/posts/scorescope-dicectf-2023/</guid>
      <description>tl;dr read output using ValueError sys.modules to print all the app modules go through the module classes and find the test case functions and re-write them to always return true intro I played DiceCTF 2023 last weekend with my team bi0s. There a were a lot of awesome web challenges. I have worked on some of the web challenges and this is the write-up for the challenge scorescope
Initial analysis We are allowed to upload a python file and the application will run several test cases on the file and if the test cases are successful it will be reflected on the page with a green colour.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
